Parapsychology Laboratory Records, 1893-1984
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence Series, 1893 and 1919-1984., 380 containers (190 lin. ft.)
  - 1954
    - Reader's Digest (Box 155)
    - Research Meeting Notes (Box 155)
    - Sa - So, (5 folders) (Box 155)
    - Sp - Sz, (2 folders) (Box 156)
    - William Sloan Associates (Box 156)
    - Ta - Tz, (2 folders) (Box 156)
    - Tomorrow Magazine (Box 156)
    - U - V, (2 folders) (Box 156)
    - Van de Castle, Robert (Box 156)
    - Van de Castle, Robert (Box 157)
    - Wa - Z, (6 folders) (Box 157)
  - 1954,Staff (Box 157)
  - 1955 (Box 158)
    - Aa - Az, (3 folders) (Box 158)
    - American Society for Psychical Research (Box 158)
    - Administration (Box 158)
    - Ba - Bk, (4 folders) (Box 158)
    - Bl - Bz, (4 folders) (Box 159)
    - Bentley, William Perry (Box 159)
    - Ca - Coq, (3 folders) (Box 159)
    - Cor - Fot, (8 folders) (Box 160)
    - Fou - Fz (Box 161)
    - Ferm, Paulie (Box 161)
    - Forwald, Haakon (Box 161)
    - Ga - Hd, (5 folders) (Box 161)
    - He - Hz, (2 folders) (Box 162)
    - Hart, Hornell (Box 162)
    - I - Ld, (5 folders) (Box 162)
    - Le - Lz, (2 folders) (Box 163)
    - Lesem, Jack (Box 163)
    - Ma - Mn, (5 folders) (Box 163)
    - Mo - Prn, (7 folders) (Box 164)
    - Pro - Pz (Box 165)
    - Parapsychology Foundation, (2 folders) (Box 165)
    - Ra - Sd, (6 folders) (Box 165)
    - Se - Tz, (9 folders) (Box 166)
    - U - Z, (8 folders) (Box 167)
    - Zorab, George (Box 167)
  - 1955, Staff (Osis) (Box 168)
    - Staff (Osis) A - Z, (2 folders) (Box 168)
  - 1955, Staff (White) A - Z, (2 folders) (Box 168)
  - 1956
    - Aa - Az, (3 folders) (Box 168)
    - Administration (Box 168)
    - American Society for Psychical Research (Box 169)
    - Ba - Bz, (6 folders) (Box 169)
    - Bentley, William Perry (Box 169)
    - Ca - Fg, (9 folders) (Box 170)
    - Fr - Hn, (9 folders) (Box 171)
    - Ho - Hz, (2 folders) (Box 172)
    - Harris, Veronica (Box 172)
    - I - Ld, (5 folders) (Box 172)
    - Le - Lz, (2 folders) (Box 173)
    - Longman, Leah (Box 173)
    - Longdon-Davies, John (Box 173)
    - Ma - Mik (Box 173)
    - Mil - Mz, (3 folders) (Box 174)
    - Morris-Pratt Institute (Box 174)
    - N (Box 174)
    - New World Foundation (Box 174)
    - Oa - Oz, (2 folders) (Box 174)
    - Pa -Pz, (4 folders) (Box 175)
    - Parapsychology Foundation, (2 folders) (Box 175)
    - Q - Rn, (2 folders) (Box 175)
    - Ro - Sn, (7 folders) (Box 176)
    - So - Sz, (3 folders) (Box 177)
    - Science (Box 177)
    - Sinclair, Upton (Box 177)
    - Soal, S.G. (Box 177)
    - Ta - V, (4 folders) (Box 177)
    - van Busschbach, J.G. (Box 177)
    - Wa - Z, (6 folders) (Box 178)
  - 1956,Staff (Osis)
    - (Osis) A - S, (3 folders) (Box 178)
    - (Osis) T - Z (Box 179)
    - Staff (Osis) Pickard, L.C. (Box 179)
    - Staff (Osis) Rivers, Olivia (Box 179)
  - 1956,Staff (White) A - Z, (5 folders) (Box 179)
  - 1957 (Box 180)
    - Aa - Az, (3 folders) (Box 180)
    - Administration (Box 180)
    - American Weekly (Box 180)
    - Ba - Bd, (2 folders) (Box 180)
    - Be - Bz, (3 folders) (Box 181)
    - Bentley, William Perry (Box 181)
    - Binski, Sigurd (Box 181)
    - Blanton, Smiley (Box 181)
    - Ca - Ck, (2 folders) (Box 181)
    - Cl - Ez, (9 folders) (Box 182)
    - Fa - Fz, (3 folders) (Box 183)
    - Fahler, Jarl (Box 183)
    - Ga - Gz, (5 folders) (Box 183)
    - Ha - Hz, (4 folders) (Box 184)
    - Hamilton, Janet (Box 184)
    - I - Kz, (3 folders) (Box 184)
    - Le - Mz, (7 folders) (Box 185)
    - McConnell, Robert A. (Box 185)
    - N (Box 186)
    - New World Foundation (Box 186)
    - O (Box 186)
    - Pa - Pz, (3 folders) (Box 186)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 186)
    - Parapsychology Foundation (Box 186)
    - Q - Rn, (2 folders) (Box 186)
    - Ro - Std, (9 folders) (Box 187)
    - Ste- Sz, (2 folders) (Box 188)
    - Schmeidler, Gertrude (Box 188)
    - Swanton, John R. (Box 188)
    - Ta - Tz, (2 folders) (Box 188)
    - Thomas, Charles C., (3 folders) (Box 188)
    - U - Wz, (5 folders) (Box 189)
    - Workshop Parapsychology (Box 189)
    - X - Z (Box 189)
  - 1957,Staff (White)
    - (White) A - O, (2 folders) (Box 189)
    - (White) P - Z, (2 folders) (Box 190)
  - 1958
    - Aa - Az, (4 folders) (Box 190)
    - Administration (Box 190)
    - American Society for Psychical Research (Box 191)
    - Ba - Bz, (6 folders) (Box 191)
    - Bentley, William Perry (Box 192)
    - Ca - Cz, (7 folders) (Box 192)
    - Da - Foq, (7 folders) (Box 193)
    - For - Gz, (7 folders) (Box 194)
    - Ghrist, W.T. (Box 195)
    - Graue, L.C. (Box 195)
    - Gwin, James B. (Box 195)
    - Ha - Hon, (5 folders) (Box 195)
    - Hoo - Hz (Box 196)
    - Haines, C. Munro (Box 196)
    - I - Kz, (6 folders) (Box 196)
    - La - Lz, (4 folders) (Box 197)
    - Lancaster, J.B. (Box 197)
    - Ma - Mar, (3 folders) (Box 197)
    - Mas - Oz, (7 folders) (Box 198)
    - O.N.R. (Box 198)
    - Pa - Pz, (4 folders) (Box 199)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 199)
    - Parapsychology Foundation (Box 199)
    - Providence Public Relations (Box 199)
    - Q - Rd, (2 folders) (Box 199)
    - Re - Sik, (7 folders) (Box 200)
    - Sil - Tg, (7 folders) (Box 201)
    - Th - Tz, (2 folders) (Box 202)
    - Thomas, Chester C. (Box 202)
    - U - Wik, (5 folders) (Box 202)
    - Wil - Z, (3 folders) (Box 203)
  - 1958,Staff (Pratt) Radio Light (Box 203)
  - 1958,Staff (White) A - Z, (2 folders) (Box 203)
  - 1959
    - Aa - Ao, (2 folders) (Box 203)
    - Ap - Az (Box 204)
    - Administration (Box 204)
    - Abrams, Stephen I. (Box 204)
    - American Society for Psychical Research (Box 204)
    - Ba - Bk, (3 folders) (Box 204)
    - Bl - Bz, (4 folders) (Box 205)
    - Bentley, William Perry (Box 205)
    - Ca - Cas, (2 folders) (Box 205)
    - Cat - Dz, (8 folders) (Box 206)
    - Ea - Fz, (7 folders) (Box 207)
    - Foos, Margaret (Box 207)
    - Fraser, J.T. (Box 207)
    - Ga - Gz, (4 folders) (Box 208)
    - Griffin, Carolyn (Box 208)
    - Ha - Hik, (3 folders) (Box 208)
    - Hil - Hz, (2 folders) (Box 209)
    - Haines House of Cords (Box 209)
    - I - J, (2 folders) (Box 209)
    - Johnson, R.W., (3 folders) (Box 209)
    - Ka - Lz, (5 folders) (Box 210)
    - Lancaster, J.B. and F. (Box 210)
    - Ma - MacJ (Box 210)
    - MacK - Nz, (8 folders) (Box 211)
    - Oa - Pz, (6 folders) (Box 212)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 212)
    - Parapsychology Foundation (Box 212)
    - Price, H.H. (Box 212)
    - Q - Sob, (10 folders) (Box 213)
    - Soc - Sz, (3 folders) (Box 214)
    - Sloan, Alfred P. Jr. (Box 214)
    - Ta - Tz, (4 folders) (Box 214)
    - U - Z, (8 folders) (Box 215)
  - 1959,Staff (Pratt) O.N.R. (Box 215)
  - 1960 (Box 216)
    - Aa - Az, (3 folders) (Box 216)
    - Abrams, Stephen (Box 216)
    - Administration, (2 folders) (Box 216)
    - American Society for Psychical Research (Box 216)
    - Ba - Beq, (2 folders) (Box 216)
    - Ber - Bz, (4 folders) (Box 217)
    - Banerjee, H.N. (Box 217)
    - Bentley, William Perry (Box 217)
    - Brown, Vernon E. (Box 217)
    - Ca - Car (Box 217)
    - Cas - Dz, (7 folders) (Box 218)
    - Ea - Fz, (5 folders) (Box 219)
    - Fraser, J.J. (Box 219)
    - Ga - Goq, (2 folders) (Box 219)
    - Gor - Gz, (2 folders) (Box 220)
    - Ha - Hz, (5 folders) (Box 220)
    - Higbee, Marie (Box 220)
    - I - Jz, (3 folders) (Box 221)
    - R.W. Johnson Co. (Box 221)
    - Jones, Stan (Box 221)
    - Ka - Kz, (3 folders) (Box 221)
    - La - Lz, (2 folders) (Box 222)
    - Lancaster, J.B. (Box 222)
    - Ma - Mh, (4 folders) (Box 222)
    - Mi - Mz, (3 folders) (Box 223)
    - Mind Science Foundation (Box 223)
    - Minto, Wallace (Box 223)
    - Na - Nz, (2 folders) (Box 223)
    - O (Box 223)
    - Pa - Pz, (4 folders) (Box 224)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 224)
    - Parapsychology Foundation (Box 224)
    - Qua - Ril, (2 folders) (Box 224)
    - Rim - Sm, (8 folders) (Box 225)
    - Sn - Sz, (4 folders) (Box 226)
    - Seaford Publishing Responses (Box 226)
    - Sinnoff, Ned (Box 226)
    - Sloan, Alfred P. (Box 226)
    - Ta - Tz, (2 folders) (Box 226)
    - U - Z, (8 folders) (Box 227)
  - 1960,Staff (Pratt) O.W.R. (Box 227)
  - 1961 (Box 228)
    - Aa - Az, (3 folders) (Box 228)
    - Administration, (2 folders) (Box 228)
    - American Society for Psychical Research (Box 228)
    - Ba - Bd, (2 folders) (Box 228)
    - Bea - Bz, (7 folders) (Box 229)
    - Banerjee, H.N. (Box 229)
    - Ca - Cz, (6 folders) (Box 230)
    - Carlson, Chester F. (Box 230)
    - Da - Dd (Box 230)
    - De - E, (4 folders) (Box 231)
    - Eckley, Patricia A. (Box 231)
    - Fa - Fn, (2 folders) (Box 231)
    - Fo - Fz (Box 232)
    - Fraser, J.T. (Box 232)
    - Ga - Haq, (5 folders) (Box 232)
    - Har - Hz, (5 folders) (Box 233)
    - Higbee, Marie (Box 233)
    - I - Jn (Box 233)
    - Jo - Jz (Box 234)
    - Johnson, E. Fred (Box 234)
    - Ka - Kz, (4 folders) (Box 234)
    - Kitselman, A.J., (2 folders) (Box 234)
    - Koestler, Arthur (Box 235)
    - La - Mas, (7 folders) (Box 235)
    - Mat - O, (8 folders) (Box 236)
    - Pa - Pz, (4 folders) (Box 237)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 237)
    - Parapsychology Foundation (Box 237)
    - Q - Rn, (2 folders) (Box 237)
    - Ro - Rz, (2 folders) (Box 238)
    - Ryzl, Milan (Box 238)
    - Sa - Sk, (4 folders) (Box 238)
    - Sl - Sz, (4 folders) (Box 239)
    - Societies for Psychical Research (Box 239)
    - Ta - Th, (2 folders) (Box 239)
    - Ti - Tz (Box 240)
    - Tenny, Kenneth (Box 240)
    - U - Wz, (6 folders) (Box 240)
    - X - Z, (2 folders) (Box 241)
  - 1962 (Box 242)
    - Aa - Az, (3 folders) (Box 242)
    - American Society for Psychical Research (Box 242)
    - Administration, (2 folders) (Box 242)
    - Ba - Beq, (2 folders) (Box 242)
    - Ber - Bz, (4 folders) (Box 243)
    - Banerjee, H.N., (2 folders) (Box 243)
    - Bentley, W.P., (2 folders) (Box 244)
    - Ca - Cq, (5 folders) (Box 244)
    - Cr - Cz (Box 245)
    - Carlson, Chester (Box 245)
    - Da - Dz, (3 folders) (Box 245)
    - Day of Acknowledgement (Box 245)
    - E (Box 245)
    - Fa - Fz, (3 folders) (Box 246)
    - Frager, J.T. (Box 246)
    - Ga - Haq, (4 folders) (Box 246)
    - Har - Hz, (4 folders) (Box 247)
    - Higbee, Marie, (2 folders) (Box 247)
    - I - Jz, (3 folders) (Box 247)
    - Ka - Lz, (5 folders) (Box 248)
    - Levitt, Zola (Box 248)
    - Lindsley Fund (Box 248)
    - Ma - MacD (Box 248)
    - MacE - Mz, (4 folders) (Box 249)
    - Maurin Foundation for Parapsychology (Box 249)
    - Mind Science Foundation (Box 249)
    - Na - Nz, (2 folders) (Box 249)
    - Nash, Carroll B. (Box 249)
    - O (Box 250)
    - O.N.R. (Box 250)
    - Pa - Pz, (3 folders) (Box 250)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 250)
    - Parapsychology Foundation (Box 250)
    - Pratt, J. Gaither (Box 250)
    - Q - Rd (Box 250)
    - Re - Rz, (3 folders) (Box 251)
    - Ryzl, Milan (Box 251)
    - Sa - Sk, (4 folders) (Box 251)
    - Sl - Sz, (4 folders) (Box 252)
    - Sherman, Harold (Box 252)
    - Societies for Psychical Research (Box 252)
    - Stone, W. Clement (Box 252)
    - Summer Short Course (Box 252)
    - Ta - Teh (Box 252)
    - Tei - U, (3 folders) (Box 253)
    - University of King's College (Box 253)
    - V - Wis, (4 folders) (Box 253)
    - Wit - Z, (2 folders) (Box 254)
  - 1963
    - Aa - Az, (3 folders) (Box 254)
    - Administration, (2 folders) (Box 254)
    - American Society for Psychical Research (Box 254)
    - Ba - Bz, (5 folders) (Box 255)
    - Bentley, William Perry (Box 255)
    - Banerjee, H.N., (2 folders) (Box 255)
    - Ca - Cz, (3 folders) (Box 256)
    - Carlson, Chester F. (Box 256)
    - Chicago Tribune (Box 256)
    - Da - Dz, (3 folders) (Box 256)
    - Dommeyer, F.C. (Box 257)
    - E - Gz, (7 folders) (Box 257)
    - Ha - Hz, (5 folders) (Box 258)
    - Higby, Marie (Box 258)
    - I - Jz, (2 folders) (Box 258)
    - Ka - Lz, (5 folders) (Box 259)
    - Lecture Series (Box 259)
    - Ma - Md, (3 folders) (Box 259)
    - Me - O, (5 folders) (Box 260)
    - Onetto, Brenio (Box 260)
    - Otani, Soji (Box 260)
    - Pa - Pq, (2 folders) (Box 260)
    - Pr - Pz (Box 261)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 261)
    - Parapsychology Foundation (Box 261)
    - Perry Foundation (Box 261)
    - Pratt, J.G., (2 folders) (Box 261)
    - Q - Rz, (5 folders) (Box 261)
    - Roll, W.G. (Box 262)
    - Ryzl, Milan, (2 folders) (Box 262)
    - Sa - Std, (4 folders) (Box 262)
    - Ste - Sz (Box 263)
    - Societies for Psychical Research (Box 263)
    - Stone, W. Clement, (2 folders) (Box 263)
    - Ta - U, (4 folders) (Box 263)
    - V - Z, (5 folders) (Box 264)
  - 1964
    - Aa - Ar, (2 folders) (Box 264)
    - As - Az (Box 265)
    - Administration, (2 folders) (Box 265)
    - American Society for Psychical Research (Box 265)
    - Ba - Brt, (4 folders) (Box 265)
    - Bru - Bz (Box 266)
    - Bayless, Raymond (Box 266)
    - Bentley, W.P. (Box 266)
    - Ca - Cz, (3 folders) (Box 266)
    - Carlson, Chester F. (Box 266)
    - Cox, Claire (Box 266)
    - Da - Dz, (3 folders) (Box 267)
    - Deon, Douglas (Box 267)
    - Dommeyer, F.C. (Box 267)
    - Ea - Fz, (5 folders) (Box 267)
    - Ga - J, (9 folders) (Box 268)
    - Ka - Mar, (8 folders) (Box 269)
    - Mas - Mz, (4 folders) (Box 270)
    - Madera de Wido, C. (Box 270)
    - Maurin Foundation for Parapsychology (Box 270)
    - Na - Or, (3 folders) (Box 270)
    - Os - Pz, (4 folders) (Box 271)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 271)
    - Parapsychology Foundation (Box 271)
    - Parapsychology Societies and Clubs (Box 271)
    - Q - Rz, (2 folders) (Box 271)
    - Ryzl, Milan (Box 271)
    - Sa - Sz, (6 folders) (Box 272)
    - Societies for Psychical Research (Box 272)
    - W. Clement Stone Foundation (Box 272)
    - Ta - Tz, (3 folders) (Box 273)
    - Tucker, Robert F. (Box 273)
    - U - Z, (6 folders) (Box 273)
  - 1965 (Box 274)
    - Aa - Az, (2 folders) (Box 274)
    - Administration (Box 274)
    - American Society for Psychical Research (Box 274)
    - Ba - Bn, (4 folders) (Box 274)
    - Bo - Cq, (7 folders) (Box 275)
    - Cr - Fz, (8 folders) (Box 276)
    - Ga - Gz, (2 folders) (Box 277)
    - Gatling, William (Box 277)
    - Granada T.V. (Box 277)
    - Ha - I, (5 folders) (Box 277)
    - Ja - Lon, (8 folders) (Box 278)
    - Loo - Mz, (7 folders) (Box 279)
    - Madera de Wico, C. (Box 279)
    - Maurin Foundation for Parapsychology (Box 279)
    - Na - Nz, (2 folders) (Box 279)
    - Noyes, Kathryn J. (Box 280)
    - O - Pz, (4 folders) (Box 280)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 280)
    - Parapsychology Foundation (Box 280)
    - Psi Workers' Newsletter (Box 280)
    - Q - Rao (Box 280)
    - Rap - Rz, (3 folders) (Box 281)
    - Research Triangle Land (Box 281)
    - Sa - Sm, (4 folders) (Box 281)
    - Sn - Sz, (3 folders) (Box 282)
    - Societies for Parapsychical Research (Box 282)
    - Steinhauser, Rick (Box 282)
    - W. Clement Stone Enterprises, (2 folders) (Box 282)
    - Ta - Tz, (2 folders) (Box 282)
    - U - Wz, (5 folders) (Box 283)
    - White, Charles W. (Box 283)
    - X - Z (Box 283)
  - 1966
    - Aa - Ao, (2 folders) (Box 283)
    - Ap - Az, (2 folders) (Box 284)
    - Administration (Box 284)
    - Ba - Bq, (4 folders) (Box 284)
    - Bri - Dn, (8 folders) (Box 285)
    - Do - E, (2 folders) (Box 286)
    - Eben, Martin, (2 folders) (Box 286)
    - Fa - Fz, (3 folders) (Box 286)
    - Form Letter Samples (Box 286)
    - Frost, Joseph S. (Box 286)
    - Ga - Hh, (7 folders) (Box 287)
    - Hi - Ld, (8 folders) (Box 288)
    - Le - Mz, (7 folders) (Box 289)
    - Minnesota Society for Psychical Research (Box 290)
    - Na - Nz, (2 folders) (Box 290)
    - Oa - Pz, (5 folders) (Box 290)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 290)
    - Psi Workers' Newsletter (Box 291)
    - Pratt, J.G. (Box 291)
    - Q - Rz, (3 folders) (Box 291)
    - Ryzl, Milan (Box 291)
    - Sa - Shh, (3 folders) (Box 291)
    - Shi - Sz, (4 folders) (Box 292)
    - Societies for Psychical Research (Box 292)
    - W. Clement Stone Enterprises (Box 292)
    - Ta - Tz, (2 folders) (Box 292)
    - Ubaldi, Pictro (Box 293)
    - V - Z, (5 folders) (Box 293)
  - 1967
    - Aa - Ao (Box 293)
    - Ap - Az (Box 294)
    - APA Symposium Paper (Box 294)
    - Avery, Harold and Marie (Box 294)
    - Ba - Bz, (6 folders) (Box 294)
    - Barker, J.C. (Box 295)
    - Biographical Sketches (Box 295)
    - Ca - Dz, (7 folders) (Box 295)
    - Duke University (Box 296)
    - Durham Morning Herald (Box 296)
    - Ea - Ez, (2 folders) (Box 296)
    - Ebon, Martin (Box 296)
    - Fa - Gz, (4 folders) (Box 296)
    - Gettings, Claire (Box 297)
    - Ha - Jz, (6 folders) (Box 297)
    - Johnson, Martin (Box 297)
    - Ka - Md, (7 folders) (Box 298)
    - Me - Mz, (3 folders) (Box 299)
    - Minnesota Society for Psychical Research (Box 299)
    - Na - O, (3 folders) (Box 299)
    - Orlick Papers (Box 299)
    - Pa - Pem (Box 299)
    - Pen - Pz, (3 folders) (Box 300)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 300)
    - Q - Sh, (4 folders) (Box 300)
    - Si - Sz, (3 folders) (Box 301)
    - W. Clement Stone Enterprises (Box 301)
    - Ta - V, (4 folders) (Box 301)
    - Van Meerton, I.R.J. (Box 302)
    - Wa - Wz, (3 folders) (Box 302)
  - 1968
    - Aa - Az, (3 folders) (Box 302)
    - Apparatus (Box 302)
    - Avery, Harold and Marie (Box 302)
    - Ba - Cn, (7 folders) (Box 303)
    - Co - Cz, (2 folders) (Box 304)
    - Carlson, Chester F. (Box 304)
    - Citadel Press (Box 304)
    - Clark, William (Box 304)
    - Da - Dz, (2 folders) (Box 304)
    - E (Box 304)
    - Ebon, Martin (Box 304)
    - Fa - Hz, (8 folders) (Box 305)
    - I (Box 306)
    - Idaho Workshop (Box 306)
    - J (Box 306)
    - Johnson, Martin (Box 306)
    - Ka - Maq, (5 folders) (Box 306)
    - Mar - Mz, (3 folders) (Box 307)
    - Moss, Thelma (Box 307)
    - N - Ph, (4 folders) (Box 307)
    - Pi - Pz, (2 folders) (Box 308)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 308)
    - Parapsychology Foundation (Box 308)
    - Price List Changes (Box 308)
    - Q - Rz, (3 folders) (Box 308)
    - Read Texts (Box 308)
    - Sa - Sch (Box 308)
    - Sci - Sz, (4 folders) (Box 309)
    - Student Inquiries (Box 309)
    - Ta - V, (3 folders) (Box 309)
    - Wa - Z, (3 folders) (Box 310)
  - 1969
    - Aa - Az, (2 folders) (Box 310)
    - American Psychological Association (Box 310)
    - Avery, Harold and Marie (Box 310)
    - Ba - Bd (Box 310)
    - Be - Deg, (8 folders) (Box 311)
    - Deh - Dz (Box 312)
    - Duke University (Box 312)
    - Dommeyer, Frederick (Box 312)
    - Ea - Gz, (6 folders) (Box 312)
    - Ha - Kz, (7 folders) (Box 313)
    - Kahler, C.R. (Box 313)
    - La - Lz, (2 folders) (Box 313)
    - Lowerie, Richard (Box 314)
    - Ma - Mz, (4 folders) (Box 314)
    - MacCotter, H.J. (Box 314)
    - N (Box 314)
    - Nesbit, Mary (Box 314)
    - Oa - Pz, (5 folders) (Box 315)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 315)
    - Personnel (Box 315)
    - Q - Rg (Box 315)
    - Rh - Rz (Box 316)
    - Richards, John Thomas (Box 316)
    - Sa - Sz, (5 folders) (Box 316)
    - Ta - Tz, (2 folders) (Box 317)
    - Thouless, Robert H. (Box 317)
    - U - Wz, (4 folders) (Box 317)
  - 1969, Staff (Feather, Salle, Rhine) (Box 317)
  - 1970
    - Aa - Az, (2 folders) (Box 317)
    - Avery, Harold and Marie (Box 318)
    - Ba - Ch, (6 folders) (Box 318)
    - Ci - D, (3 folders) (Box 319)
    - Duke University (Box 319)
    - Dommeyer, F.C. (Box 319)
    - E - Goq, (4 folders) (Box 319)
    - Gor - Lz, (8 folders) (Box 320)
    - Ma - Pz, (8 folders) (Box 321)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 322)
    - Parapsychology Foundation (Box 322)
    - Ra - Sz, (7 folders) (Box 322)
    - Senators and President (Box 322)
    - Ta - Z, (6 folders) (Box 323)
  - 1970, Staff (Tucker) (Box 323)
  - 1971
    - A (Box 323)
    - American Society for Psychical Research (Box 323)
    - Avery, Harold and Marie (Box 323)
    - Ba - D, (7 folders) (Box 324)
    - Dommeyer, Frederick C. (Box 325)
    - Duke University (Box 325)
    - E - Hd, (5 folders) (Box 325)
    - He - J, (4 folders) (Box 326)
    - Johnson, Martin (Box 326)
    - Ka - Lz, (4 folders) (Box 326)
    - Ma - Mz, (3 folders) (Box 327)
    - Maurin Foundation (Box 327)
    - Mitchell, Edgar D., (2 folders) (Box 327)
    - N - O, (2 folders) (Box 327)
    - Pa - Pz, (2 folders) (Box 328)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 328)
    - Q - Sd, (4 folders) (Box 328)
    - Se - Wh, (8 folders) (Box 329)
    - Wi - Z, (2 folders) (Box 330)
  - 1972
    - Ba - Bz, (4 folders) (Box 330)
    - Brown, B. Ray (Box 330)
    - Ca - Cn (Box 330)
    - Co - Cz, (2 folders) (Box 331)
    - Cavendish, Richard (Box 331)
    - Cavendish, Richard; Rhine mss, (4 folders) (Box 331)
    - Cavendish, Richard; L.E. Rhine mss (Box 331)
    - Da - Dz, (2 folders) (Box 331)
    - Dommeyer, F.C. (Box 331)
    - E - Fk, (2 folders) (Box 331)
    - Fl - Jz, (7 folders) (Box 332)
    - Johnson, Martin (Box 332)
    - Ka - Kz, (2 folders) (Box 332)
    - La - Lz, (2 folders) (Box 333)
    - Levy, Walter J. (Box 333)
    - Ma - Mz, (4 folders) (Box 333)
    - Maurin Foundation for Parapsychology (Box 333)
    - Mitchell, Edgar D. (Box 333)
    - N (Box 334)
    - Neihardt, John G. (Box 334)
    - O - Pz, (4 folders) (Box 334)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 334)
    - Q - Rz, (2 folders) (Box 334)
    - Rao, K.R. (Box 335)
    - Roll, William G. (Box 335)
    - Sa - Tz, (7 folders) (Box 335)
    - U - Z, (6 folders) (Box 336)
  - 1973
    - Aa - Az, (2 folders) (Box 336)
    - American Society for Psychical Research (Box 336)
    - Avery, Harold and Marie (Box 336)
    - Ba - Dh, (7 folders) (Box 337)
    - Di - Dz (Box 338)
    - Dommeyer, F.C. (Box 338)
    - E (Box 338)
    - Ebon, Martin (Box 338)
    - Fa - Gz, (4 folders) (Box 338)
    - Ha - Kz, (7 folders) (Box 339)
    - La - Lz, (2 folders) (Box 340)
    - Lockhead, G.R. (Box 340)
    - Long, Joseph K. (Box 340)
    - Ma - Mn, (3 folders) (Box 340)
    - Mo - N, (2 folders) (Box 341)
    - Newton, Grant (Box 341)
    - O - Pz, (5 folders) (Box 341)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 341)
    - Q - So, (7 folders) (Box 342)
    - Sp - Won, (8 folders) (Box 343)
    - Wz - Z, (2 folders) (Box 344)
  - 1974
    - Aa - Bz, (4 folders) (Box 344)
    - Biographical Materials–Staff Members (Box 344)
    - Ca - Cz, (3 folders) (Box 344)
    - CRM Books (Box 345)
    - D - I, (8 folders) (Box 345)
    - Ja - Lz, (5 folders) (Box 346)
    - Levy, Walter J., (2 folders) (Box 346)
    - Ma - Mz, (2 folders) (Box 346)
    - McDonald Award (Box 346)
    - Maurin Foundation (Box 346)
    - N - Pz, (4 folders) (Box 347)
    - Parapsychological Association (Box 347)
    - Poltergeists (Box 347)
    - Price Lists (Box 347)
    - Ro - Rz, (2 folders) (Box 347)
    - Records of Manuscripts and Papers Loaned (Box 348)
    - Review Meetings (Box 348)
    - Sa - Sz, (4 folders) (Box 348)
    - Students (Box 348)
    - T - Wh, (3 folders) (Box 348)
    - Wi - Z (Box 349)
  - 1975
    - A - E, (7 folders) (Box 349)
    - F (Box 350)
    - Fair, J.D. (Box 350)
    - G - L, (8 folders) (Box 350)
    - Ma - Mz, (3 folders) (Box 351)
    - Maurin Foundation (Box 351)
    - N - P, (3 folders) (Box 351)
    - Parapsychological Assocication (Box 351)
    - Parapsychology Foundation (Box 351)
    - Q - Rz, (2 folders) (Box 351)
    - Sa - Sz, (3 folders) (Box 352)
    - Summer Study Program (Box 352)
    - T - Z, (3 folders) (Box 352)
    - White, Charles W., (2 folders) (Box 352)
  - 1976
    - A (Box 352)
    - Ba - Dz, (4 folders) (Box 353)
    - Dowsing (Box 353)
    - E (Box 353)
    - Ebon, Martin (Box 353)
    - F - K, (5 folders) (Box 353)
    - L - M, (2 folders) (Box 354)
    - Manuel (Box 354)
    - Maurin Foundation (Box 354)